<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mark Edmondson - Personal Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.markedmondson.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mark Edmondson - Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Mark Edmondson - All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 11:14:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.markedmondson.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>American cultural imperialism via American social media platforms</title>
      <link>http://www.markedmondson.me/posts/american-cultural-imperialism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 11:14:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.markedmondson.me/posts/american-cultural-imperialism/</guid>
      <description>Image based on Raising the Flag on Iwo Jima By Joe Rosenthal
Emigrating from the UK to Denmark has given me a lot, but one unexpected insight is how the structural setup of a country affects the values that filter down to its citizens. On the surface Denmark and the UK are similar countries but after 10 years living in another&amp;rsquo;s framework I have come to appreciate the subtle differences. When I&amp;rsquo;m asked about the prime difference now I sum it up in &amp;ldquo;Trust&amp;rdquo;, from which flows Danish contentment and enfranchisement of its citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book reviews - 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.markedmondson.me/posts/books-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 12:16:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.markedmondson.me/posts/books-2019/</guid>
      <description>I had a GoodReads challenge to read 24 books this year, I didn&amp;rsquo;t quite make it but I did read very big books. I will try to read smaller books in 2020 :)
My top fiction books of 2019 Exhalation by Ted Chiang https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/46347126-exhalation
Sanne first introduced Ted Chiang&amp;rsquo;s first book of sci-fi short stories, Stories of Your Life and Others as it was the source of one of our favourite films, Arrival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truth According to Me</title>
      <link>http://www.markedmondson.me/posts/truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 20:04:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.markedmondson.me/posts/truth/</guid>
      <description>I feel a need for a line in the sand on what I think is true.
1. The scientific method is the best way to obtain objective reality As defined by Popper, to differentiate between subjective and objective truths, a theory needs to make predictions that are verified by repeatable experiments. This method of enquiry is what science is founded upon, and lets us enjoy aeroplanes, TVs and computer chips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Edmondson Presentations</title>
      <link>http://www.markedmondson.me/static/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 11:12:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.markedmondson.me/static/presentations/</guid>
      <description>Presentation links Gathering in one place links to presentations I&amp;rsquo;ve made over the years.
 Use Cases for R in the Cloud - an online webinar for an Australian Web Analytics Wednesday with Moe Kiss, showing how I&amp;rsquo;m using R in the Google Cloud in October 2020. Evolving R with Docker and the Cloud - Rv1.0.0&amp;rsquo;s 20th Birthday celebRation, Copenhagen 2020-02-29 R at scale on the Google Cloud Platform - CopenhagenR, 2019-05-19 Man vs Machine - Superweek 2019 and Web Analytics Wednesday Copenhagen - 2019-02-01 #rstats lessons for #measure - Digital Analytics Congres, Utrecht.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>